<resources>
    <string name="app_name">15seconds</string>
    <string name="welcome_messege_0">Hello!</string>
    <string name="exercisesButtonName">Exercises</string>
    <string name="calendarButtonName">Calendar</string>
    <string name="showoffButtonName">Share</string>
    <string name="settingsButtonName">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="day_availability">Action hours:</string>
    <string name="from">From</string>
    <string name="to">To</string>
    <string name="exercise_time">Exercise Time:</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="hyphenSettings">-</string>
    <string name="exerciseJJacksDescription">Jumping jacks is a physical jumping exercise performed by jumping to a position with the legs spread wide and the hands touching overhead, sometimes in a clap, and then returning to a position with the feet together and the arms at the sides.</string>
    <string name="exercisePushupsDescription">Push-up is a common calisthenics exercise beginning from the prone position, or the front leaning rest position known in the military. By raising and lowering the body using the arms, push-ups exercise the pectoral muscles, triceps, and anterior deltoids, with ancillary benefits to the rest of the deltoids, serratus anterior, coracobrachialis and the midsection as a whole.</string>
    <string name="exercisePlankDescription">Plank is an isometric core strength exercise that involves maintaining a position similar to a push-up for the maximum possible time.</string>
    <string name="exerciseSitupDescription">Sit-up begins with lying with the back on the floor, typically with the arms across the chest or hands behind the head and the knees bent in an attempt to reduce stress on the back muscles and spine, and then elevating both the upper and lower vertebrae from the floor until everything superior to the buttocks is not touching the ground.</string>
    <string name="exerciseSquatDescription">Squat movement begins from a standing position. The movement is initiated by moving the hips back and bending the knees and hips to lower the torso and accompanying weight, then returning to the upright position.</string>
    <string name="exerciseSupermanDescription">Superman exercise begin by lying straight with face down on the floor or exercise mat. Your arms should be fully extended in front of you. This is the starting position. Simultaneously raise your arms, legs, and chest off of the floor and hold this contraction for 2 seconds. Remember to exhale during this movement. Slowly begin to lower your arms, legs and chest back down to the starting position while inhaling.</string>
    <string name="exerciseJRopeDescription">Jumping rope is as its name explain, simply... jumping above the rope. To do it, you have to hold the rope with hands at about hip height and elbows slightly bent, keeping your upper arms close to your sides. Your chest should be out and your shoulders back and down. Make your jumps small and land on the balls of your feet.</string>
</resources>
